const quizQuestions = [
    {
        question: "1. What dates does the purge fall on in 'The Purge'?",
        choices: ["December 25- December 26", "Dec. 31st- Jan 1", "March 21 - March 22", "May 13 - May 14"],
        correctAnswer: "March 21 - March 22",
        image: "./assets/images/"
    },

    {
        question: "2. What is the name of the Villain in 'The Ring'?",
        choices: ["Camille", "Samara", "Audrey", "Naomi "],
        correctAnswer: "Samara",
        image: "assets/images/"
    },
    {
        question: "3. Which movie was based on a video game?",
        choices: ["Texas Chainsaw Massacre", "Silent Hill", "Child's Play", "Halloween "],
        correctAnswer: "Silent Hill",
        image: "assets/images/"
    },

    {
        question: "4. In 'Saw', where was Amanda's key hidden?",
        choices: ["In the intestines of the guy next to her", "In a scorching hot oven", "Behind her eye", "In a safe covered in spikes"],
        correctAnswer: "In the intestines of the guy next to her",
        image: "assets/images/"
    },
    {
        question: "5. Which horror movie came out in 1979?",
        choices: ["Alien", "Black Christmas", "A Nightmare on Elm Street", "Poltergeist"],
        correctAnswer: "Alien",
        image: "assets/images/"
    },

    {
        question: "6. Which horror film does the quote 'The Power of Christ compels you!' come from?",
        choices: ["An American Haunting", "Halloween", "A Nightmare on Elm Street", "The Exorcist"],
        correctAnswer: "The Exorcist",
        image: "assets/images/"
    },
    {
        question: "7. What is not one of the rules for taking care of a Mogwai in 'Gremlins'?",
        choices: ["Cannot Feed Them Wheat", "No Bright Light", "Never Get Them Wet", "Do Not Feed After Midnight"],
        correctAnswer: "Cannot Feed Them Wheat",
        image: "assets/images/"
    },

    {
        question: "8. Which Horror film among these is based on a true story?",
        choices: ["Get Out", "The Conjuring", "Halloween", "Jeepers Kreepers"],
        correctAnswer: "Get Out",
        image: "assets/images/"
    },

    {
        question: "9. True or False: Michael Meyers escaped from a federal penitentiary.",
        choices: ["True","False"],
        correctAnswer: "False",
        image: "assets/images/"
    },

    {
        question: "10. How many movies are made for the Saw Series?",
        choices: ["4","8","10","5"],
        correctAnswer: "8"
    },

];
const funImages = [
    "'/assets/images/creepy smile.gif'",
    '/assets/images/winner.gif',
    '/assets/images/happy.gif',
    '/assets/images/celebrate3.gif',
    './assets/images/celebrate.gif',
    './assets/images/celebrate1.gif',
    './assets/images/celebrate2.gif',
];
const sadImages =[
    './assets/images/scared.gif',
    './assets/images/lost.gif',
    './assets/images/failed.gif',
    './assets/images/ring.gif',
    './assets/images/creepy smile.gif',
];